<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Yogyam</string>
    <string name="text1">Pain in the belly (abdomen) can come from conditions affecting a variety of organs.\nAlthough abdominal pain can arise from the tissues of the abdominal wall that surround the abdominal cavity (for example, skin and abdominal wall muscles), the term abdominal pain generally is used to describe pain originating from organs within the abdominal cavity (for example, beneath the skin and muscles).</string>
    <string name="text2">Pain areas: in the joints, ankle, back, fingers, hands, muscles, neck, or wrist.\nPain types: can be intermittent or sharp.\nPain circumstances: can occur while sitting\nMuscular: decreased range of motion, difficulty walking, or muscle weakness\nJoints: stiffness, tenderness, or swelling\nAlso common: flare, physical deformity, redness, or stiff neck</string>
    <string name="text3">Cough: can occur at night, during exercise, can be chronic, dry, with phlegm, mild, or severe\nRespiratory: difficulty breathing, wheezing, breathing through the mouth, fast breathing, frequent respiratory infections, rapid breathing, or shortness of breath at night\nAlso common: chest pressure, flare, anxiety, early awakening, fast heart rate, or throat irritation</string>
    <string name="text4">Signs and symptoms of back pain may include:\n1.Muscle ache\n2.Shooting or stabbing pain\n3.Pain that radiates down your leg\n4.Limited flexibility or range of motion of the back</string>
    <string name="text5">Inflammation of the lining of bronchial tubes, which carry air to and from the lungs.\nSymptoms of bronchitis include coughing up thickened mucus and shortness of breath.\nAcute bronchitis is often caused by a viral respiratory infection and improves by itself.</string>
    <string name="text6">In contrast to the flu, a common cold can be caused by many different types of viruses. The condition is generally harmless and symptoms usually resolve within two weeks.\nSymptoms include a runny nose, sneezing and congestion.</string>
    <string name="text7">Constipation most commonly occurs when waste or stool moves too slowly through the digestive tract or cannot be eliminated effectively from the rectum, which may cause the stool to become hard and dry.\nThough occasional constipation is very common, some people experience chronic constipation that can interfere with their ability to go about their daily tasks.</string>
    <string name="text8">The persistent feeling of sadness or loss of interest that characterises major depression can lead to a range of behavioural and physical symptoms. These may include changes in sleep, appetite, energy level, concentration, daily behaviour or self-esteem. Depression can also be associated with thoughts of suicide.\nPossible causes include a combination of biological, psychological and social sources of distress.</string>
    <string name="text9">Diabetes describes a group of metabolic diseases in which the person has high blood glucose (blood sugar), either because insulin production is inadequate, or because the body\'s cells do not respond properly to insulin, or both. Patients with high blood sugar will typically experience polyuria (frequent urination), they will become increasingly thirsty (polydipsia) and hungry (polyphagia).</string>
    <string name="text10">Sore, tired, burning or itching eyes.\nWatery or dry eyes.\nBlurred or double vision.\nHeadache.\nSore neck, shoulders or back.\nIncreased sensitivity to light.\nDifficulty concentrating.\nFeeling that you cannot keep your eyes open.</string>
    <string name="text11">This disorder may develop when bile (produced by the gallbladder) does not pass through the ducts into the small intestine as it usually does. Passage of bile may be slowed or blocked because\nGallstones, which may be too small to be detected by ultrasonography, are present.</string>
    <string name="text12">A tension headache is generally a diffuse, mild to moderate pain in your head that\'s often described as feeling like a tight band around your head. A tension headache (tension-type headache) is the most common type of headache.\nSigns and symptoms of a tension headache include:\nDull, aching head pain,Sensation of tightness or pressure across your forehead or on the sides and back of your head, Tenderness on your scalp, neck and shoulder muscles</string>
    <string name="text13">Indigestion is an uncomfortable feeling of fullness, pain, or burning in your upper abdomen.\nSymptoms of indigestion include\nabdominal pain,\nheartburn or acid indigestion (acid reflux),\nbloating and gas,\nnausea,\nacidic taste in the mouth,\nstomach discomfort,\nconstipation or diarrhea, and\ndecreased appetite.</string>
    <string name="text14">Insomnia is difficulty falling asleep or staying asleep, even when a person has the chance to do so.\nPeople with insomnia can feel dissatisfied with their sleep and usually experience one or more of the following symptoms:\nfatigue,low energy, \ndifficulty concentrating, \nmood disturbances, and \ndecreased performance in work or at school.\nInsomnia is a common sleep problem for adults.</string>
    <string name="text15">Major function of the kidneys is to remove waste products and excess fluid from the body in the form of urine.The production of urine involves highly complex steps of excretion and re-absorption.\nYou may have an increased risk for kidney disease if you:\nare older
\nhave diabetes or have high blood pressure
\nhave a family member who has chronic kidney disease</string>
    <string name="text16">The liver plays an important role in the metabolism of proteins\nSigns and symptoms of liver disease include:\nSkin and eyes that appear yellowish (jaundice)\nAbdominal pain and swelling\nSwelling in the legs and ankles\nDark urine color\nPale stool color, or bloody or tar-colored stool\nNausea or vomiting\nLoss of appetite\nTendency to bruise easily</string>
    <string name="text17">Typically, a woman will begin to experience menopause symptoms around her mid-40\'s as her body\'s reproductive capability comes to the end.\nThis prolonged stage of gradually falling and fluctuating hormone levels is called perimenopause, which can last upwards of two years before a woman's final period. For most women, perimenopause symptoms end at menopause; however, some symptoms will continue.</string>
    <string name="text18">Some women experience a host of physical and/or emotional symptoms just before and during menstruation.\nA period disorder can have following symptoms:
\nabnormal uterine bleeding (AUB), which may include heavy menstrual bleeding, no menstrual bleeding (amenorrhea) or bleeding between periods (irregular menstrual bleeding)
\ndysmenorrhea (painful menstrual periods)
\npremenstrual syndrome (PMS)
\npremenstrual dysphonic disorder (PMDD)</string>
    <string name="text19">In the emergence of neurasthenic disorders, a whole list of causes of all kinds is of great importance. Among them, for example, exposure to toxic substances, deficiency of vitamins, immunity disorders, oncological processes, etc. Often the disease occurs against the background of the disorder of metabolic processes.\nNeurasthenic syndrome is more often observed in people at the peak of activity - from 20 to 45 years.</string>
    <string name="text20">Obesity is a medical condition in which excess body fat has accumulated to the extent that it may have a negative effect on health.\nOn average, obese people have a greater energy expenditure than their normal counterparts due to the energy required to maintain an increased body mass.\nExcessive body weight is associated with various diseases and conditions, particularly cardiovascular diseases, diabetes mellitus type 2, obstructive sleep apnea, certain types of cancer, osteoarthritis,and asthma.</string>
    <string name="text21">Piles is another term for hemorrhoids. Hemorrhoids are collections of inflamed tissue in the anal canal. They contain blood vessels, support tissue, muscle, and elastic fibers.\nPiles are collections of tissue and vein that become inflamed and swollen.
\nThe size of piles can vary, and they are found inside or outside the anus.
\nPiles occur due to chronic constipation, chronic diarrhea, lifting heavy weights, pregnancy, or straining when passing a stool.</string>
    <string name="text22">Poor posture can be a large contributor to neck and back pain.Excess pressure — caused by poor posture, extra weight and engaging in high-impact sports — accelerates the degeneration of the discs and joints in the spine that can lead to painful conditions like arthritis and herniated discs. A person working in a shipping warehouse lifting heavy boxes every day may develop posture problems due to lower back strain, while office workers may have posture issues in their shoulders from hunching over a computer desk each day.</string>
    <string name="text23">As a woman, the pelvic organs are held in place by the pelvic floor, but sometimes, the pelvic floor becomes so weak that it causes pelvic organ prolapse. It is estimated that about one in three women will have issues with prolapse in their lifetime, which makes this condition one major concern for females.\nA few contributing factors that may make you more at risk for organ prolapse include:\nVaginal delivery during childbirth,
\nAging,Being overweight, A chronic cough,Prolonged issues with constipation</string>
    <string name="text24">With this condition, the urinary stream may be weak or stop and start. In some cases, it can lead to infection, bladder stones and reduced kidney function.\nPeople may experience:
\nUrinary: dribbling after urination, excessive urination at night, frequent urination, sense of incomplete bladder emptying, urge to urinate and leaking, or weak urinary stream
\nAlso common: incontinence or sexual dysfunction</string>
    <string name="text25">Reproductive health implies that people are able to have a responsible, satisfying and safer sex life and that they have the capability to reproduce and the freedom to decide if, when and how often to do so.\n Disorders of reproduction include birth defects, developmental disorders, low birth weight, preterm birth, reduced fertility, impotence, and menstrual disorders.</string>
    <string name="text26">Rheumatoid arthritis is a chronic inflammatory disorder that can affect more than just your joints. In some people, the condition also can damage a wide variety of body systems, including the skin, eyes, lungs, heart and blood vessels.\nSigns and symptoms of rheumatoid arthritis may include:
\nTender, warm, swollen joints
\nJoint stiffness that is usually worse in the mornings and after inactivity
\nFatigue, fever and weight loss</string>
    <string name="text27">Pain originates in the spine and radiates down the back of the leg.\nPain areas: in the back, buttocks, hip, or lower extremities
\nPain types: can be mild, severe, radiating, or sharp
\nPain circumstances: can occur due to injury or while sitting
\nMuscular: difficulty walking or muscle weakness
\nSensory: leg numbness or pins and needles</string>
    <string name="text28">Sexual dysfunction symptoms can manifest in different ways depending on the type and cause of dysfunction. The signs and symptoms of sexual dysfunction include:
\nLack of sexual desire
\nDifficulty becoming aroused
\nPain during intercourse</string>
    <string name="text29">Acute sinusitis can be triggered by a cold or allergies and may resolve on its own. Chronic sinusitis lasts up to eight weeks and may be caused by an infection or growths.\nSymptoms include headache, facial pain, runny nose and nasal congestion.</string>
    <string name="text30">Skin irregularities that are typically symptoms of a skin disorder include:
\nraised bumps that are red or white
\na rash, which might be painful or itchy
\nscaly,rough skin or peeling skin
\nulcers,open sores or lesions
\ndry, cracked skin
\ndiscolored patches of skin, loss of skin pigment, excessive flushing
\nfleshy bumps, warts, or other skin growths
\nchanges in mole color or size</string>
    <string name="text31">Throat problems are common. You\'ve probably had a sore throat. The cause is usually a viral infection, but other causes include allergies, infection with strep bacteria or the leaking of stomach acids back up into the esophagus, called GERD.
\nOther problems that affect the throat include
\nTonsillitis - inflammation of the tonsils\nCroup - inflammation, usually in small children, which causes a barking cough
\nLaryngitis - swelling of the voice box, which can cause a hoarse voice or loss of voice</string>
    <string name="text32">Thyroid disease is a medical condition that affects the function of the thyroid gland (the endocrine organ found at the front of the neck that produces thyroid hormones).\n The symptoms of thyroid disease vary depending on the type. There are three general types: 1) hypothyroidism (low function) caused by not having enough thyroid hormones; 2) hyperthyroidism (high function) caused by having too much thyroid hormones; 3) structural abnormalities, most commonly an enlargement of the thyroid gland</string>
    <string name="text33">Varicose veins are generally benign. The cause of this condition is not known.\nFor many people, there are no symptoms and varicose veins are simply a cosmetic concern. In some cases, they cause aching pain and discomfort or signal an underlying circulatory problem.</string>
    <string name="text34">Trapped wind is a very common condition causing pain or discomfort around the digestive system, usually due to a build up of pressure in your stomach or abdomen.\nCommon symptoms of trapped wind are:
\nA bloated stomach or abdomen
\nFlatulence or burping
\nStomach cramps, Rumbling or gurgling noises in your stomach
\nPain when you bend over, lie down or during exercise
\nPain that moves around the body</string>
    <string name="text35">Wrinkles are the lines and creases that form in your skin. Some wrinkles can become deep crevices or furrows and may be especially noticeable around your eyes, mouth and neck.\nAlthough genetics mainly determine skin structure and texture, sun exposure is a major cause of wrinkles, especially for fair-skinned people. Other factors, such as pollutants and smoking, also contribute to wrinkling.</string>
    <string name="exercises">Asanas</string>
    <string name="view_exercises">View Asanas</string>
    <string name="view_exercise">View Asana</string>
    <string name="exercise_name">Asana Name</string>
</resources>
